Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Chancellor Records, 1933-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1933-2011, UWM Archival Collection 46; 220.4 cubic ft. (224 boxes) 2 film reels 718 digital files (539 MB)
  - 5. Schroeder Administration Records, 1986-1998
    - Drop Rates, 1990-1996 (Box 156)
    - Drugfree Workplace Act, Drugfree Schools Act, 1988-1989 (Box 156)
    - Economic Benefits Committee, 1989-1998, 2 folders (Box 156)
    - Editorial Board Meetings, 1996 (Box 156)
    - Education Media Policy Committee, 1995-1998 (Box 156)
    - Educational Policy and Community Studies, 1990-1997, 3 folders (Box 156)
    - Egypt, 1988-1989 (Box 156)
    - Electrical Energy Shortage, 1997-1998 (Box 156)
    - Electronic Publication of Information, 1996-1997 (Box 156)
    - E-Mail, 1994-1997, 2 folders (Box 156)
    - Emeritus Status, 1989-1997, 4 folders (Box 156)
    - Employee Assistance Program Advisory Committee, 1989-1996, 2 folders (Box 156)
    - Employee Interchange Agreements, 1992-1995 (Box 156)
    - English Proficiency, 1991-1996, 2 folders (Box 157)
    - Enrollment Management, 1989-1997, 2 folders (Box 157)
    - Enrollment Services
      - 1991-1997, 2 folders (Box 157)
      - Admissions, 1990 (Box 157)
      - Registrar, 1990 (Box 157)
    - Enrollment Statistics, 1996-1997 (Box 157)
    - Environmental Health and Safety, 1992-1997 (Box 157)
    - Equal Opportunity Policy, 1992-1997 (Box 157)
    - Ethics Board (Code of Ethics), 1988-1995 (Box 157)
    - Evaluation of Administrators, 1993-1998 (Box 157)
    - Executive Salary Plan, 1989 (Box 157)
    - EXPO, 1992 (Box 157)
    - Faculty Academic Planning and Budget Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 157)
    - Faculty Appeals and Grievances Committee, 1994-1998 (Box 157)
    - Faculty Development, 1992-1994 (Box 157)
    - Faculty Disciplinary Procedures, 1992-1997 (Box 157)
    - Faculty Luncheons, 1989 (Box 157)
    - Faculty Review and Development Plan, 1995-1997 (Box 157)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1990-1997, 2 folders (Box 157)
    - Faculty Salary Equity Study, 1994-1996, 2 folders (Box 157)
    - Faculty Senate
      - 1990-1995 (Box 157)
      - Budget Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 157)
      - Committee on Affirmative Action in Faculty Employment, 1993-1995 (Box 157)
      - Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 157)
      - Rules Committee, 1989-1998 (Box 157)
    - Faculty Workload, 1992-1996, 2 folders (Box 157)
    - Federal Direct Student Loan Program, 1995-1996 (Box 157)
    - Fellowships, 1994-1997 (Box 157)
    - Financial Aid, 1990-1997, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - Financial Services, 1990 (Box 158)
    - Fine Arts Planning Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 158)
    - First Amendment, 1992-1997 (Box 158)
    - First Friday, 1990-1997 (Box 158)
    - Firstar/First Wisconsin, 1990-1994 (Box 158)
    - Foreign Language and Linguistics, 1997 (Box 158)
    - Foreign Language Requirement, 1990-1992 (Box 158)
    - Foundation, UWM, 1996-1997 (Box 158)
    - Foundation Capital Campaign, 1995-1996 (Box 158)
    - Foundations, General, 1991-1997, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - Four-Year Graduation Program, 1996 (Box 158)
    - Frankel Decision, 1990-1992 (Box 158)
    - Freshmen Scholars, 1996-1997 (Box 158)
    - Fromkin Memorial Lecture, 1993-1997, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - Fudan University, 1985-1987 (Box 158)
    - Fulbright Scholars, 1989-1997 (Box 158)
    - Fundraising, 1992-1996 (Box 158)
    - Gateway to Engineering, Science, and Technology, 1990-1997 (Box 158)
    - Gay and Lesbian Studies Certificate Program, 1994-1995 (Box 158)
    - Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Issues Advisory Committee, 1992-1996, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - Gender Equity Project, Academic Staff Category A, 1991-1995 (Box 158)
    - Gender Equity Review Team, 1991-1992 (Box 158)
    - Gender Equity, 1992-1993 (Box 158)
    - Gender/Race Equity Project, 1996 (Box 158)
    - General Education Administration, 1996-1998, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - General Education Requirements, 1987-1997, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - Glass Ceiling, 1992-1993 (Box 158)
    - Goethe Universität, 1982-1988 (Box 158)
    - Golden Key National Honor Society, 1991-1992 (Box 158)
    - Governor, State of Wisconsin, 1990-1998, 2 folders (Box 158)
    - Governor's Dental Commission, 1992-1993 (Box 158)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, 1990-1993 (Box 158)
    - Graduate School, 1991-1998 (Box 158)
    - Graduate School/Foundation Research Awards, 1990-1998 (Box 158)
    - Graduate School and Research, 1989-1990 (Box 158)
    - Graduate School Working Group, 1996-1998 (Box 158)
    - Great Books Certificate Program, 1994-1995 (Box 152)
    - Great Lakes Research Facility, Advisory Council, 1987 (Box 159)
    - Great Lakes Water Institute, 1998 (Box 159)
    - Greater Milwaukee Committee, 1991-1998, 3 folders (Box 159)
    - Greater Milwaukee Education Trust Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 159)
    - Greene Geological Museum
      - 1993-1996 (Box 159)
      - Special Committee on the Future of the Greene Museum, 1995 (Box 159)
    - Harbin Institute of Technology, 1990 (Box 159)
    - Health and Welfare, Ad Hoc Campus Coordinating Committee, 1990 (Box 159)
    - Hebrew Studies, 1991 (Box 159)
    - Hebrew University of Jerusalem, 1988 (Box 159)
    - Hearing Impaired, 1992 (Box 159)
    - Hefter Conference Center, 1991-1994, 2 folders (Box 159)
    - Higher Education Aids Board, 1989-1991, 2 folders (Box 159)
    - Higher Education Cable Consortium, 1990-1992 (Box 159)
    - Hispanic Association of Colleges and Universities, 1990 (Box 159)
    - History of UWM, 1990-1993 (Box 159)
    - Holidays, 1994-1997 (Box 159)
    - Honorary Degrees Candidates, 1989-1990 (Box 159)
    - Honorary Degrees Committee, 1989-1996 (Box 159)
    - Honorary Societies, 1989-1995 (Box 159)
    - Honors Convocation, 1989-1993 (Box 159)
    - Honors Program, 1990-1997, 2 folders (Box 159)
    - Human Relations Program, 1990 (Box 159)
    - Human Resources, 1993-1996, 3 folders (Box 159)
    - IBM Partners in Excellence Program, 1995 (Box 159)
    - Illinois Scholar Incentive Award Program, 1996 (Box 159)
    - Inauguration, 1991-1992, 2 folders (Box 159)
    - Indirect Cost Funds, 1990 (Box 159)
    - Industrial Research and Technology Transfer, 1990 (Box 159)
    - Information and Media Technologies, 1995 (Box 159)
    - Information Technology Plan, 1992 (Box 159)
    - Interinstitutional Agreements, 1990-1995, 2 folders (Box 159)
    - International Agreements, 1990-1992 (Box 159)
    - International Studies and Programs, 1990-1998, 2 folders (Box 159)
    - Institute of World Affairs, 1990-1997, 2 folders (Box 159)
    - Institute on Race and Ethnicity, 1994-1995 (Box 159)
    - Institutional Competition Review Committee, 1989 (Box 159)
    - Institutional Research, 1990-1997, 2 folders (Box 159)
    - Israeli Independence Day, 1991-1992 (Box 159)
    - Instructional Materials, Use, Ownership, and Control of, 1998 (Box 159)
    - Instructional Television Fixed Service, 1984 (Box 159)
    - Jagiellonian University, 1978-1990 (Box 160)
    - James, Charlie, 1983-1996 (Box 160)
    - Jilin University of Technology (China), 1987-1992 (Box 160)
    - Johnson, Robert Wood Foundation, 1995 (Box 160)
    - Joint Administrative Committee on Academic Programs, 1991-1996, 2 folders (Box 160)
    - Joint Committee on Employment Relations, 1997 (Box 160)
    - Joint Finance Committee, 1997 (Box 160)
    - JOVE Program, 1995 (Box 160)
    - Justus-Liebig-Universität Giessen (Germany), 1981-1993 (Box 160)
    - Kenilworth Building, 1993-1995 (Box 160)
    - Kennan Forum, 1990-1993 (Box 160)
    - Keulks, George W., 1997 (Box 160)
    - Klotsche Center, 1989-1998, 2 folders (Box 160)
    - Klotsche, J. Martin, 1973-1997, 2 folders (Box 160)
    - Ko-Thi Dance Company, Inc., 1990 (Box 160)
    - Kunkle Parking Structure, 1990 (Box 160)
    - Laboratory for Surface Studies, 1995-1998 (Box 160)
    - Laboratory Modernization, 1991-1996 (Box 160)
    - Languages, Literature, and Linguistics, 1996 (Box 160)
    - Lapham Hall Science Center, 1988-1995, 2 folders (Box 160)
    - Late Night Events, 1998 (Box 160)
    - Latin American Studies Certificate Program, 1994-1995 (Box 160)
    - Latin Student Union, 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box 160)
    - Latinos for Justice, 1995 (Box 160)
    - Learning Skills and Educational Opportunity, 1992-1995 (Box 160)
    - Learning Technology Center, 1996 (Box 160)
    - Leaves, 1987-1991 (Box 160)
    - Lectures Committee, 1994-1998 (Box 160)
    - Legal Affairs, 1991-1998, 3 folders (Box 160)
    - Legislation, University Related, 1992-1997, 2 folders (Box 160)
    - Legislative Audit Bureau
      - 1990-1996, 2 folders (Box 160)
      - Teaching Load Audit, 1993 (Box 160)
    - Library, 1990-1998, 4 folders (Box 161)
    - Library Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 161)
    - Light Rail, 1992-1993 (Box 161)
    - Limited Appointments, 1991-1995 (Box 161)
    - Limited-Term Employment, 1983-1993 (Box 161)
    - Lobbying, 1989-1995 (Box 161)
    - Logo, 1989-1998 (Box 161)
    - Maier Chair, 1988-1996, 2 folders (Box 161)
    - Management Flexibilities, 1996 (Box 161)
    - Manufacturing Extension Services Proposal, Working Group, 1994 (Box 161)
    - Marietta House, 1974-1989 (Box 161)
    - Marketing Plan, 1996 (Box 161)
    - Marquette University, 1991-1997, 2 folders (Box 161)
    - Masters in Industrial and Labor Relations, 1991 (Box 161)
    - Masters in Public Administration, 1991 (Box 161)
    - Maternity Leave, 1991 (Box 161)
    - Math/Science Education, 1991 (Box 161)
    - Mayor's Office, 1991-1998 (Box 162)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1989 (Box 162)
    - Medical College of Wisconsin, 1990-1998, 2 folders (Box 162)
    - Memberships, 1994-1996 (Box 162)
    - Metropolitan Milwaukee Association of Commerce, 1991-1997, 2 folders (Box 162)
    - Metropolitan Milwaukee Civic Alliance, 1990-1994 (Box 162)
    - Mexico, 1990 (Box 162)
    - Middle East Crisis, 1991 (Box 162)
    - Middle East Technical University, 1991-1992 (Box 162)
    - Midwest University Energy Consortium, 1990-1995 (Box 162)
    - Military Leave, 1991-1992 (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Area Technical College, 1990-1998, 3 folders (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee, City of, 1990-1995, 2 folders (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee, County of, 1990-1992 (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee County Research Park, 1991-1992 (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Courier, 1988 (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Foundation, 1991-1994 (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Graduate Assistants Association, 1991-1998, 2 folders (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Guarantee, 1990-1991 (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Initiative, 1988-1998, 2 folders (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Jewish Companion, 1989 (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Journal/Sentinel, 1988-1997, 2 folders (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Metropolitan Sewerage District, 1989-1992 (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Professional Fellows Program, 1988 (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Public Schools, 1990-1997, 2 folders (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Public Schools/UWM Coordinating Committee, 1990 (Box 162)
    - Milwaukee Regional Medical Center, 1990 (Box 162)
    - Minority Affairs Council (UWM), 1989-1993 (Box 162)
    - Minority Program Brochure, 1987 (Box 162)
    - Minority Student Recruitment Committee, 1991 (Box 162)
    - Mitchell Hall, 1991-1994 (Box 162)
    - Moi University (Kenya), 1986 (Box 162)
    - Muhammed, Khalid Abdul, 1994 (Box 162)
    - Multiculturalism, 1991 (Box 162)
    - Name Changes, 1997-1998 (Box 163)
    - Naming of Buildings or Spaces Within, 1988-1993 (Box 163)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges
      - 1989-1998, 4 folders (Box 163)
      - 102nd Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 163)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association
      - 1990-1997, 4 folders (Box 163)
      - Annual Convention, 1993 (Box 163)
      - Self-Study Committee, 1998 (Box 163)
    - National Science Foundation, 1990-1996, 3 folders (Box 163)
    - NEDA Mines, 1993 (Box 163)
    - Network Library System, 1987 (Box 163)
    - New Faculty, 1990 (Box 163)
    - Non-Resident Tuition Appeals Committee, 1992-1995 (Box 163)
    - Non-Resident Tuition Remission, 1997-1998 (Box 163)
    - Nontraditional Students Study, 1996 (Box 163)
    - North Central Association
      - 1992-1998, 2 folders (Box 163)
      - Annual Reports, 1985-1991 (Box 163)
      - Focused Evaluation, 1998 (Box 163)
      - Self-Study Report, 1995 (Box 163)
      - Site Visit, 1995 (Box 163)
    - Northeast Normal University, 1983-1993 (Box 163)
    - Office of Diversity/Compliance
      - 1995-1998, 2 folders (Box 155)
      - Advisory Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 155)
    - Open House, 1996-1997 (Box 164)
    - Open Meetings Law, 1991 (Box 164)
    - Open Positions, External, 1998 (Box 164)
    - Outreach and Continuing Education, 1990-1998, 4 folders (Box 164)
    - Outreach Service Agreements, 1996 (Box 164)
    - Outside Activity Reports, General Correspondence, 1991-1998 (Box 164)
    - Overload Payments, 1995 (Box 164)
    - Paradise Beach, 1994 (Box 164)
    - Parking and Transit, 1992-1998, 2 folders (Box 164)
    - Parking Structure, 1995-1996 (Box 164)
    - Peace Studies, 1988-1995, 2 folders (Box 164)
    - Percent for Art Program, 1992-1998 (Box 164)
    - Ph.D. Programs, 1997-1998 (Box 164)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1991 (Box 164)
    - Physical Environment Committee
      - 1990-1996, 3 folders (Box 164)
      - Subcommittees, 1991-1997, 2 folders (Box 164)
    - Physical Plant Services, 1994-1997 (Box 164)
    - Physical Plant Work Environment Survey Report, 1995 (Box 164)
    - Physical Therapy Program, 1989-1990 (Box 164)
    - Placement and Career Development, 1985-1990 (Box 165)
    - Planning Documents, 1994-1995 (Box 165)
    - Planning Process, 1989-1991 (Box 165)
    - Policies, Miscellaneous, 1996-1998 (Box 165)
    - Policy Committee for Campus-Wide Information, 1995 (Box 165)
    - Political Activities by Employees, 1993-1995 (Box 165)
    - Political Correctness, Issue of, 1991-1993 (Box 165)
    - Potawatomi Bingo, 1993 (Box 165)
    - Pre-College Academy, 1996 (Box 165)
    - Pre-College Programs, 1991-1994 (Box 165)
    - Professional Sports Counseling Panel, 1996 (Box 165)
    - Professional Theater Training Program, 1990-1996, 2 folders (Box 165)
    - Program Array Review, 1997-1998 (Box 165)
    - Program Revenue Activities, 1994 (Box 165)
    - Promotions, 1990-1997, 3 folders (Box 165)
    - Protests, undated (Box 165)
    - Public Policy Forum, 1991-1997, 2 folders (Box 165)
    - Public Relations, 1998 (Box 165)
    - Puelicher, Jack, 1987-1989 (Box 165)
    - Quality Education Commission, 1994-1997 (Box 165)
    - Quality Reinvestment Program, 1991-1993 (Box 165)
    - Race and Ethnicity, 1990-1993 (Box 165)
    - Racism, 1989-1990 (Box 165)
    - Radio Interview (JHS), 1996 (Box 165)
    - Remarks, 1992-1993, 5 folders (Box 166)
    - Report on Minority Students at UWM, 1987 (Box 166)
    - Research, 1991-1992 (Box 166)
    - Research Centers of Excellence, 1988 (Box 166)
    - Research Incentive Program, 1991-1995, 2 folders (Box 166)
    - Research Infrastructure Committee, 1994 (Box 166)
    - Research Misconduct Policy, 1989-1997 (Box 166)
    - Research Plan, 1992-1997 (Box 166)
    - Research Policy Committee, 1989-1995, 2 folders (Box 166)
    - Residence Inventories, 1976 (Box 166)
    - Retired Faculty Association, 1994-1997 (Box 166)
    - Retirement Legislation, 1996-1998 (Box 166)
    - Return to Work Policy, 1993 (Box 166)
    - Renaissance Program, 1992 (Box 166)
    - ROTC/Office Education/Military Science, 1983-1990 (Box 166)
    - Sabbatical Leave, 1990-1998, 3 folders (Box 166)
    - Sabin/Greene, 1995 (Box 166)
    - Salary Adjustment Guidelines, 1988-1998, 3 folders (Box 166)
    - Salary Increases, 1993-1997 (Box 166)
    - Sandburg Hall Addition, 1994 (Box 167)
    - Sandburg Hall Administrative Council, 1990-1996 (Box 167)
    - Sandburg Residence Halls, 1991-1993 (Box 167)
    - Satellite Site Working Group, 1997 (Box 167)
    - SAVE Commission, 1994-1995 (Box 167)
    - School of Allied Health Professions
      - 1990-1998, 4 folders (Box 147)
    - School to Work Program, 1996 (Box 167)
    - School of Architecture and Urban Planning
      - 1984-1998, 5 folders (Box 148)
      - New Building, 1989-1991 (Box 148)
      - Wisconsin Space Grant Consortium, 1991-1997 (Box 148)
    - School of Business Administration
      - 1988-1996 (Box 149)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 150)
      - Building, 1990-1995 (Box 150)
      - Strategic Plan/Lateral Review, 1996-1997 (Box 150)
    - School of Education, 1990-1998, 3 folders (Box 156)
    - School of Fine Arts, 1990-1997, 3 folders (Box 158)
    - School of Library and Information Science, 1991-1997, 3 folders (Box 161)
    - School of Library and Information Science, Accreditation, 1976-1995 (Box 161)
    - School of Nursing
      - 1989-1998, 4 folders (Box 163)
      - Accreditation, 1991-1992 (Box 164)
    - School of Social Welfare
      - 1990-1996, 3 folders (Box 168)
      - Accreditation, 1977-1986, 1996, 2 folders (Box 169)
      - Title IV-E, 1992 (Box 169)
    - School of the Arts, 1998 (Box 148)
    - Schroeder Appointment Congratulatory Letters, 1990-1991 (Box 167)
    - Search and Screen Committees
      - 1991-1997 (Box 167)
      - Academic Affairs, Vice Chancellor, 1991-1992 (Box 167)
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, Dean, 1989-1990 (Box 167)
      - Business Administration, Dean, 1996-1997 (Box 167)
      - Chancellor, 1990, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 167)
      - Development and Alumni Affairs, Chief Advancement Officer, 1991-1992 (Box 167)
      - Education, Dean, 1993-1995 (Box 167)
      - Engineering and Applied Science, Dean, 1995-1997, 2 folders (Box 167)
      - Equal Opportunity Programs, Assistant Chancellor, 1993-1994 (Box 167)
      - Fine Arts, Dean, 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 167)
      - Graduate School, Dean, 1996-1997 (Box 167)
      - Letters and Science, Dean, 1994-1996, 2 folders (Box 167)
      - Nursing, Dean, 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 167)
      - Outreach and Continuing Education, 1986 (Box 167)
      - Outreach and Continuing Education, 1996-1998 (Box 168)
      - Secretary of the University, 1997 (Box 168)
      - Social Welfare, Dean, 1988-1992, 2 folders (Box 168)
      - Student Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, 1991-1992 (Box 168)
      - Student Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, Final Report, 1992 (Box 168)
      - University Relations, Assistant Chancellor, 1991-1992 (Box 168)
    - Secretary of the University, 1994-1998 (Box 168)
    - Seeds of Crisis, 1988-1994, 2 folders (Box 168)
    - Segregated Fee, 1989-1994, 2 folders (Box 168)
    - Seijo University (Tokyo, Japan), 1987-1989 (Box 168)
    - Sexual Assaults, Annual Report to UWS, 1992 (Box 168)
    - Sexual Harassment (Policy), 1990-1995 (Box 168)
    - Sexual Harassment Awareness Committee, 1992-1995, 2 folders (Box 168)
    - Sexual Harassment Grievance Committee, 1989-1992 (Box 168)
    - Shanghai Jiao Tong University, 1982-1987 (Box 168)
    - Shaw Scholars Program, 1988-1990 (Box 168)
    - Sick Leave Policy, 1988-1989 (Box 168)
    - Smith, Clifford, 1986 (Box 168)
    - Smoking, 1991-1994 (Box 168)
    - Social Science Research Facility, 1990 (Box 168)
    - Software Copyright Policy, 1996 (Box 169)
    - Solomon Amendment, 1983-1984 (Box 169)
    - Southeast Asian Students, 1991 (Box 169)
    - Southeastern Wisconsin Research Complex, 1988-1989 (Box 169)
    - Space, 1993 (Box 169)
    - Spaights Plaza Committee, 1994 (Box 169)
    - Speech File, 1990-1994, 25 folders (Box 169)
    - Speech File, 1995-1998, 188 folders (Box 170)
    - Speeches/Remarks, 1996-1998, 4 folders (Box 171)
    - Spies, 1997 (Box 171)
    - Sponsored Research Programs, 1998 (Box 171)
    - SPRE Program, 1994 (Box 171)
    - State Building Commission, 1992 (Box 171)
    - State Employees Combined Campaign, 1989-1997, 3 folders (Box 171)
    - Steering Committee for Strategic Planning in Engineering and Technology, 1989 (Box 171)
    - Steering Committee on Status of Academic Staff, 1996 (Box 171)
    - Strategic Alliances, 1997 (Box 171)
    - Strategic Plan, 1991-1997, 3 folders (Box 171)
    - String Academy of Wisconsin, 1996-1997 (Box 171)
    - Student Academic Disciplinary Procedures (UWS 14), 1991 (Box 171)
    - Student Accessibility Center, 1992-1994 (Box 171)
    - Student Administrative Data System Enhancement, 1998 (Box 171)
    - Student Affairs, 1989-1997, 3 folders (Box 171)
    - Student Association, 1990-1997, 3 folders (Box 172)
    - Student Complaints, Report of, 1996-1997 (Box 172)
    - Student Conduct Hearing Committee, 1991-1996 (Box 172)
    - Student Non-Academic Disciplinary Procedures (UWS 17), 1989-1992 (Box 172)
    - Student Organization Disciplinary Review Committee, 1993 (Box 172)
    - Student Organizations, 1994 (Box 172)
    - Student Social Security Numbers, 1998 (Box 172)
    - Student Technology Fee, 1995 (Box 172)
    - Study of UW System in 21st Century, 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 172)
    - Sullivan-Spaights Advisory Board, 1992-1995 (Box 172)
    - Sullivan-Spaights Professorship, 1987-1996 (Box 172)
    - Surface Studies, Laboratory, 1988-1991 (Box 172)
    - Surveys and Questionnaires, 1990-1998, 4 folders (Box 172)
    - Take our Daughters to Work Day, 1995 (Box 172)
    - Target MD Program, 1987-1992 (Box 172)
    - Task Force on UWM and the Future of Metropolitan Milwaukee, 1987-1991 (Box 173)
    - TAUWP (The Association of University of Wisconsin Professionals), 1991-1996, 2 folders (Box 173)
    - Teaching Award, 1990-1997, 2 folders (Box 173)
    - Telemarketing Campaign, 1994-1997 (Box 173)
    - Tempo, 1995-1998, 2 folders (Box 173)
    - Ten Chimneys, 1997 (Box 173)
    - TIAA-CREF, 1997-1998 (Box 173)
    - Title IX, 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 173)
    - Title IX Task Force Report, 1978 (Box 173)
    - Tokyo Metropolitan University, 1984 (Box 173)
    - Total Quality Management, 1991-1992 (Box 173)
    - Trojan Case, 1991 (Box 173)
    - Trust Funds, 1994 (Box 173)
    - Tuition and Fees, 1990-1995, 2 folders (Box 173)
    - Uihlein Fellowships, 1991 (Box 173)
    - Uihlein House, 1981-1986 (Box 173)
    - Unclassified Personnel Guidelines, 1989-1990 (Box 173)
    - Undergraduate Education, 1990-1996, 2 folders (Box 173)
    - Undergraduate Experience Committee Blue Ribbon Task Force, 1992-1994 (Box 173)
    - Undergraduate Transfer Policy, 1990 (Box 173)
    - Union, 1990-1992 (Box 173)
    - Union Policies/Banners and Protests in UWM Concourse, 1992 (Box 173)
    - Union Policy Board, 1996 (Box 173)
    - United Arab Emirates University, 1993 (Box 173)
    - United Council of UW Student Governments, 1993-1994 (Box 173)
    - United States Department of Education, 1990-1996, 3 folders (Box 173)
    - United States Department of Labor, Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs
      - 1991 (Box 173)
      - 1992-1994, 3 folders (Box 174)
      - Implementation Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 174)
      - Implementation Working Group, 1994 (Box 174)
    - United States Government Agencies, Miscellaneous, 1988-1991, 2 folders (Box 174)
    - University Art Museum, 1989-1995, 3 folders (Box 174)
    - University Art Museum Policy Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 174)
    - University Art Museum Special Task Force, 1994-1996 (Box 174)
    - University Center for Continuing Education, 1996 (Box 174)
    - University Committee, 1991-1997, 2 folders (Box 174)
    - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research, 1988 (Box 174)
    - University Insurance Association, 1991-1992 (Box 174)
    - University Lecture, 1992-1994 (Box 174)
    - University Police, 1991-1998, 2 folders (Box 174)
    - University Professor, 1995 (Box 174)
    - University Relations Committee, 1988-1994, 2 folders (Box 174)
    - University School, 1988-1992 (Box 174)
    - UW-Center System, 1990-1994, 3 folders (Box 174)
    - UW Day (Technology Transfer Week), 1992 (Box 174)
    - UW-Eau Claire, 1992-1997 (Box 174)